# Jose Loperena Monzón

### **Personal Statement**

I am creative and a motivated self-starter who loves to discover new things every day. Thanks to my knowledge gained in IT .With the years, I have also developed in different zones such as in PHP, HTML, CSS, C# (.NET Framework), Java and MySqI. This has helped me to develop new software and gain experience in software development. My goal now is to further my understanding of IT.

# Education

#### NHL Stenden 2018-2023

Currently, a 4th year student

Advancing my knowledge in different aspects of IT such as GoLang, Kotlin

Also include basic python knowledge.

Oakley College 2003 - 2018

A Levels 2016-2018.

3 A Levels

Cambridge international A Level in IT (Information Technology) Score: D

Geography Score: B

Spanish Score: A\*

### Cambridge exams

Cambridge Advanced (CAE) 2018 Score: 183

Cambridge English First Certificate (FCE) 2017 Score: 176

#### **IELTS Conversion:**

Overall: 6.5 Reading: 5.5 Use of English: 5.5 Writing: 6.5 Listening: 6.5

Speaking:7.5

IGCSEs-2014-2016

8 GCES's including Spanish (A\*), German (B) and ICT (C)

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## Halqasid Ltd,

June 2016

Halqasid S.L. is a business which imports and sells equipment for people with physical disabilities. Here, I helped re-organising the database they had. Also, help them reorganize the layout of the products within this shop. From this I have developed different ICT skills such as the use and development of databases and the different skills required to constantly have it organized.

#### ASML,

August 2021- January 2022

Worked in ASML in 5 sub projects where my problem solving skills as well as Python skills were put into challenge. With this, I also developed my skills on the microsoft premises such as Sharepoint and TypeScript to develop a better Sharepoint page for the company

#### ZenZorrito,

February 2023 - June 2023

Finished working on a CI/CD pipeline project which made the feedback loop of the different engineers much shorter as well as improving the pipeline speed of the company making it much faster and improving the time that the different engineers need to wait for different steps that run on the pipeline .

# **Volunteering**

# Greenpeace, Las Palmas de Gran Canaria

September 2016-2017

Planning a beach clean-up at a local beach. Distributing leaflets with advice on how to protect the environment. With this I have developed communication skills and now, I am confident enough to talk in public. I also learned how people can have different opinions and how not to take these opinions personally. This has made me develop 2 important skills such as how to give feedback and how to manage it.

#### Girl Up club

2014 -2018

Organizing events such as a Movie night and bake sales to raise money for the girl up charity. The skills which I developed from my volunteering were communication skills as I was constantly talking with a diversity of people that also had a different culture. I also developed my money managing skills as we did different bake sales and movie nights. This meant that we needed to manage the money after the different events to see where the money could go within the society.

# **Transferable Skills**

IT skills include: use of editing software for photography and videos such as Photoshop and OpenShot. Use of animation software such as Animate CC. Use of Microsoft Office and google docs, sheets and slides. In depth knowledge of Database and Excel including the use of reports, formula and functions

Communication skills: including fluent Spanish and English. Ability to communicate effectively with the public.

**Teamwork skills:** from work experience, work with Greenpeace and through being a member of a local basketball team my teamwork skills have been developed positively.

Problem solving skills: demonstrated through reorganization of database during work experience.